<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Learning | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/deep-learning/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Deep Learning</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/deep-learning/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>The art</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is surrounded by art every day. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a person&amp;rsquo;s life without art. It dates back to ancient times, when primitive people learned to draw on rocks, make tools, and make sounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, the culture has changed. But unlike people who lived, lived their lives and died, she remained. There are works by leading composers: Bach, Mozart, Beethoven. They have passed through the years and continue to please many people. We may not know the authors of famous works, but we hear and see the creation itself. A person may not know that the Mona Lisa was written by Leonardo da Vinci, and &amp;ldquo;To Elise&amp;rdquo; by Beethoven, but these works are priceless. And all because feelings are connected in them. In any kind of art - painting, literature, music, theater - feelings are embedded. The author, drawing a portrait, adds something of his own - his feelings, thoughts. The viewer perceives everything in his own way as well.In any work of art, he sees his own, his inner world. So, for example, one book can make a movie, a TV series, show a performance, but it will all be different, because everyone has their own ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art helps people discover more of themselves, realize themselves, go into their inner world - the world of their ideas and dreams. It helps to break away from the reality as it is, and get into a completely different, opposite world. That is why the role of art is invaluable in human life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The task of man is to preserve art. Yes, you can restore later to do something new. But it will be different, not what it really was. We must appreciate and cherish what we have. If this does not happen, if people stop appreciating art, the world will be doomed to destruction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
